Jasmine Drumright

Data Analyst



ABOUT ME

I am an insurance analyst specializing in AD&D enrollment processing and QA.

With my background in museum interpretation and data entry, I discovered data analytics as a way to combine these two experiences into a career.

I seek to transition to a data analyst position to continue my passion for data and technical skills from attending the parttime Data Analytics Bootcamp at Nashville Software School.

SKILLS

- SQL (PostgreSQL)
 - EDA
 - Joins, CTEs
- Power BI
- Tableau
- Python
 - NumPy
 - Pandas, geopandas
 - Matplotlib (Seaborn)
- Jupyter Notebook
- Excel
 - Advanced lookups
 - Mail merge to Word
- GitHub
- AS400
- Salesforce
- Bilingual in English and Cantonese

EDUCATION

Nashville Software School

Certificate, Data Analytics expected Jun 2022

University of British Columbia

BA, Linguistics May 2017

DATA ANALYTICS EXPERIENCE

Nashville Software School

Data Analytics Apprentice (remote)

Nashville, TN, USA

Jan 2022 - present

SQL Projects

- Lahman Baseball: Exploratory data analysis from a relational database to investigate trends among baseball players, managers, and games from 1871-2016
- App Trader: Exported query results from App Store and Play Store tables to present the Top 10
 Apps yielding the highest ROI with additional recommendations for a Pi Day debut
- · Data Analyst Job Titles: Query practice with aggregations and filters using Indeed job postings

BI Tools Projects

- Power BI: Designed a dashboard from the 2018 Central Park Squirrel Census data showing the breakdown of fur colors, time of day spotted, location, activities, and threatened reactions
- *Tableau*: Created a two-dashboard story using PS4 game sales data from Kaggle showing the bestselling games, publishers, and genres from 2013-2018 in Europe and North America

Python Projects

- GDP and Internet Use: Imported CSV files from UNdata into Jupyter Notebook to visualize top
 and bottom 5 countries with respect to annual GDP and internet use using Seaborn
- **Head On Collisions**: Cleaned CSV data to map head on collisions reported on clear days in the South precinct of Davidson County using geopandas

Excel Projects

- Yelp Charlotte: Analyzed Yelp data between three tables using Excel PowerPivot to identify user preferences and popular businesses in Charlotte, NC
- 2016 Tax Returns: Developed an interactive dashboard to guide decision making at Hand Up
 America in where to focus tax filing assistance for elderly and low income groups in the US
- City Cemetery: Designed an event poster from cleaned and filtered burial data in Excel

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Franklin Madison

Member Services Analyst (hybrid remote)

Data Entry Temp

Franklin, TN, USA

Richmond, BC, Canada

Feb 2018 - Mar 2019

Jun 2017 - Jan 2018

May 2016 - Dec 2016

Apr 2021 - present Jul 2020 - Mar 2021

- Format and send daily error reports in Excel to department supervisors
- Resolve record errors by manually matching incoming enrollments to existing customer database
- · Complete assigned project tracker tasks from Client Services in Salesforce to meet SLAs
- Perform customer account changes through AS400 while exceeding metrics rate by 75%
- Print and mail response letters for ineligible enrollments using mail merge

City of Richmond

Head Recreation Attendant

Recreation Attendant

Special Events Intern (UBC Arts Internship Program)

Trained and supervised five new employees in museum eneration

- Trained and supervised five new employees in museum operations
- Coordinated with 41 partner sites to create a map brochure for the City's largest arts event
- Led guided museum tours to 400 visitors per day resulting in extended operating hours
- · Operated community center front desk in daily point of sale and membership renewals